{
"question": "さあ",
"answer": "さあ"
},
{
"question": "どうも",
"answer": "どうも"
},
{
"question": "じゃあ",
"answer": "じゃあ"
},
{
"question": "其れから",
"answer": "それから"
},
{
"question": "ええ",
"answer": "ええ"
},
{
"question": "ノート",
"answer": "ノート"
},
{
"question": "ボタン",
"answer": "ボタン"
},
{
"question": "デパート",
"answer": "デパート"
},
{
"question": "トイレ",
"answer": "トイレ"
},
{
"question": "其れでは",
"answer": "それでは"
},
{
"question": "明後日",
"answer": "あさって"
},
{
"question": "何れ",
"answer": "どれ"
},
{
"question": "二十歳",
"answer": "はたち"
},
{
"question": "彼方",
"answer": "あちら"
},
{
"question": "では",
"answer": "では"
},
{
"question": "フィルム",
"answer": "フィルム"
},
{
"question": "温い",
"answer": "ぬるい"
},
{
"question": "四日",
"answer": "よっか"
},
{
"question": "カレンダー",
"answer": "カレンダー"
},
{
"question": "七日",
"answer": "なのか"
},
